<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fundayo - Invest in profitable rental properties in Africa</title>
    <link>https://www.fundayo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fundayo - Invest in profitable rental properties in Africa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.fundayo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons Why African Americans Should Start Investing In Africa</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-african-americans-should-start-investing-in-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-african-americans-should-start-investing-in-africa/</guid>
      <description>I believe this is Africa’s moment, for the very important reason that Africa is showing signs of real progress and renewal.
- Myles Wickstead (Head of the Secretariat to the UK Commission for Africa)
 Just two years ago, Marvel’s “Black Panther” generated an unprecedented enthusiasm about the prospects of Africa. The fictitious, prosperous, futuristic, powerful, and proud African nation “Wakanda” salutes black culture by shedding light on black excellence and stimulating our imaginations of what success can look like for Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Effortlessly Invest Back Home in Less than 5 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/effortlessly-invest-back-home-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/effortlessly-invest-back-home-africa/</guid>
      <description>Once viewed as a “brain drain”, migrants are increasingly viewed as a resource for promoting economic development back in their home countries.
- Nicely put by Benjamin Graham in his book Investing in the Homeland
 Let’s face it, we’ve all been there, moving to a foreign country in search of a better life, working twice as hard to build a successful career and support family back home even though the odds are against you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Interpretation and Definitions Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>