<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>invest on Fundayo - Invest in profitable rental properties in Africa</title>
    <link>https://www.fundayo.com/tags/invest/</link>
    <description>Recent content in invest on Fundayo - Invest in profitable rental properties in Africa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.fundayo.com/tags/invest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Should you &#34;Go Back to Africa&#34; to Invest?</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/should-you-go-back-to-africa-to-invest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/should-you-go-back-to-africa-to-invest/</guid>
      <description>When you’re Black in Europe or in the United States, you’ve probably been told to “Go back to Africa” several times. In 2019, Donald Trump used this expression to attack four congresswomen on his ex-favorite social media platform in a series of tweets saying &amp;ldquo;go back and help fix the totally broken and crime infested places from which they came. Then come back and show us how it is done.&amp;rdquo; Usually, this expression is a continued rhetoric that the West is too full to welcome people from other countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons Why African Americans Should Start Investing In Africa</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-african-americans-should-start-investing-in-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-african-americans-should-start-investing-in-africa/</guid>
      <description>I believe this is Africa’s moment, for the very important reason that Africa is showing signs of real progress and renewal.
- Myles Wickstead (Head of the Secretariat to the UK Commission for Africa)
 Just two years ago, Marvel’s “Black Panther” generated an unprecedented enthusiasm about the prospects of Africa. The fictitious, prosperous, futuristic, powerful, and proud African nation “Wakanda” salutes black culture by shedding light on black excellence and stimulating our imaginations of what success can look like for Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Effortlessly Invest Back Home in Less than 5 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/effortlessly-invest-back-home-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/effortlessly-invest-back-home-africa/</guid>
      <description>Once viewed as a “brain drain”, migrants are increasingly viewed as a resource for promoting economic development back in their home countries.
- Nicely put by Benjamin Graham in his book Investing in the Homeland
 Let’s face it, we’ve all been there, moving to a foreign country in search of a better life, working twice as hard to build a successful career and support family back home even though the odds are against you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>