<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>africa on Fundayo - Invest in profitable rental properties in Africa</title>
    <link>https://www.fundayo.com/tags/africa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in africa on Fundayo - Invest in profitable rental properties in Africa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.fundayo.com/tags/africa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #1</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-1/</guid>
      <description>The African continent is famous for its poverty, but many people don’t know the complete reason why Africa is still so poor. While we all have a vague idea such as corruption, colonisation, or foreign interference, all these reasons ignore WHY any of those things can happen in the first place. This article series seeks to change that, we will look from the point when African countries were rich and powerful, how over the centuries Africa lost its wealth and why Africa hasn’t been able to crawl out of it’s poverty while so many other countries and former colonies have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #2</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-2/</guid>
      <description>How did African slavery grow from a relatively small market where slaves had rights, into a large system of warfare where slaves became property to be sold to the highest bidder? Well, this was as a result of rising demands for slaves. The African slave trade evolved into a system where traders would go to Africa to buy slaves and put as many as they could fit onto their ships. They would then sail to the Americas where those slaves were sold to work to death in the fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #3</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-3/</guid>
      <description>How did African slavery grow from a relatively small market where slaves had rights, into a large system of warfare where slaves became property to be sold to the highest bidder? Well, this was as a result of rising demands for slaves. The African slave trade evolved into a system where traders would go to Africa to buy slaves and put as many as they could fit onto their ships. They would then sail to the Americas where those slaves were sold to work to death in the fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #4</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-4/</guid>
      <description>So why did African countries getting their Independence not lead to African nations becoming wealthy? Well, history has shown us that former colonies can become wealthy countries such as New Zealand, Ireland, or South Korea, yet not a single country in Africa is considered a ‘developed country’. And this as a result of the state reason in which the colonizers left Africa. When people don’t have the skills to run a country, when communities don’t connect to each other, and when prosperity is already rare, it becomes very difficult for the leaders of that country to bring prosperity to that country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #5</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-5/</guid>
      <description>So why did African countries choose a system that prevents them from becoming wealthy in the first place? Well, the reason is that this was the system which they inherited from their former colonizers; where the colonial government controlled nearly every aspect of the colony’s economy. And if they wanted to switch to a free market system like Western Europe, East Asia, or North America then they would need business people and entrepreneurs to set up new businesses, but the problem with this was that Africans weren’t allowed to run their own businesses under colonialism, so the entrepreneurial attitude didn’t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #6</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-6/</guid>
      <description>So how were the newly emerged African elites going to protect themselves from a coup and stay in power? Well, by taking the money intended for economic development and handing them out as salaries to powerful government officials to keep them happy enough so they wouldn’t start a rebellion. But whereas colonies had oversight from their European government who would fire anyone getting too corrupt, the new leaders had no such oversight and to show just how incompetent some of these governments were, in the Central African Republic, the government didn’t even keep proper records of financial transactions, ignored budgets in favour of in-the-moment decisions, and government salaries could often be 3 or 4 months late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #7</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-7/</guid>
      <description>So what were the 3 major issues Africa faced in the 1980s? The first was that the infrastructure in Africa started to break down and raw materials became far more difficult to export. The second was that Africans who did receive a proper education decided to move to other countries where they would receive a better salary, meaning that Africa was losing its smartest and best educated people. And the third was the fall of the Soviet Union.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is Africa Still So Poor? - #8</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-is-africa-still-so-poor-part-8/</guid>
      <description>Africa is in a much better place in the 21st century with a burgeoning Tech scene and lots of foreign investments in the Fintech space, however, Africa is still facing many issues and there are some trends worth mentioning. Africa is the least prepared for climate change while probably suffering the most under it, ⅓ of all children are malnourished, ⅓ of children don’t finish high school, extremists find it easy to recruit the vast number of poor unemployed young people, epidemics are common across the continent with Ebola being just one among many, and the economic development of Africa is limited to certain countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should you &#34;Go Back to Africa&#34; to Invest?</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/should-you-go-back-to-africa-to-invest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/should-you-go-back-to-africa-to-invest/</guid>
      <description>When you’re Black in Europe or in the United States, you’ve probably been told to “Go back to Africa” several times. In 2019, Donald Trump used this expression to attack four congresswomen on his ex-favorite social media platform in a series of tweets saying &amp;ldquo;go back and help fix the totally broken and crime infested places from which they came. Then come back and show us how it is done.&amp;rdquo; Usually, this expression is a continued rhetoric that the West is too full to welcome people from other countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons Why African Americans Should Start Investing In Africa</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-african-americans-should-start-investing-in-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/why-african-americans-should-start-investing-in-africa/</guid>
      <description>I believe this is Africa’s moment, for the very important reason that Africa is showing signs of real progress and renewal.
- Myles Wickstead (Head of the Secretariat to the UK Commission for Africa)
 Just two years ago, Marvel’s “Black Panther” generated an unprecedented enthusiasm about the prospects of Africa. The fictitious, prosperous, futuristic, powerful, and proud African nation “Wakanda” salutes black culture by shedding light on black excellence and stimulating our imaginations of what success can look like for Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How You Can Effortlessly Invest Back Home in Less than 5 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/effortlessly-invest-back-home-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fundayo.com/blog/effortlessly-invest-back-home-africa/</guid>
      <description>Once viewed as a “brain drain”, migrants are increasingly viewed as a resource for promoting economic development back in their home countries.
- Nicely put by Benjamin Graham in his book Investing in the Homeland
 Let’s face it, we’ve all been there, moving to a foreign country in search of a better life, working twice as hard to build a successful career and support family back home even though the odds are against you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>